# MLADEN ŽIVOJINOVIĆ

### **ABOUT ME**

Web developer with experience in developing simple websites and web applications. I specialize in JavaScript and Wordpress, I have experience in working with React as well. I am always learning new things and working on a daily basis to improve my knowledge.

#### CONTACT

- 060/18-50-415
- ✓ mladenzivojinovic96@gmail.com
- Smederevo
- in https://www.linkedin.com/ in/mladen-zivojinovic/
- https://github.com/Mlade n1996

## **SKILLS**

- HTML5
- React
- CSS3
- PHP
- Bootstrap
- MySQL
- Sass
- Wordpress
- JavaScript
- GIT
- GatsbyJS

### LANGUAGES

English - intermediate level

#### **EDUCATION**

 School of Electrical and Computer Engineering of Applied Studies - Belgrade

2015 - 2018

New Computer Technologies Average grade : 8.93

Economic - trade school Smederevo
2011 - 2015

Insurance officer

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Front-end Internship - Golux Technologies
Beograd

OCT 2019 - JAN 2020

Developing an application in React

 Student demonstrator - School of Electrical and Computer Engineering of Applied Studies - Belgrade OCT 2017 - JUN 2018

Laboratory demonstator from course Introduction to internet technology and Human Computer interaction.

#### **PROJECTS**

Gifty - <a href="https://gifty.rs/">https://gifty.rs/</a>

E-commerce gift shop Wordpress (Woocommerce)

Eat Fit - <u>https://eatfit.rs/</u>

E-commerce shop healthy food Wordpress (Woocommerce)

Movie App- <a href="https://myreactmovieapp.netlify.com/">https://myreactmovieapp.netlify.com/</a>

A movie display application React i TheMovieDB API

MacaPeruvian - <a href="http://macaperuvian.com/">http://macaperuvian.com/</a>

Website for cure sales Wordpress

Gatsby website - <a href="https://myreactwebsite.netlify.com/">https://myreactwebsite.netlify.com/</a>

Multilanguage website React i GatsbyJS